Contact

9994819879 (Mobile) sraghu30@hotmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/raghus-185a65152 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Hypertext Transfer Protocol (HTTP)
Distributed Systems
Exploratory Testing

Certifications

SelectorsHub Certification Program Robocorp Automation Developer Level II

Robocorp Automation Developer Level I

Robocorp AutomationOps Analyst HackerRank Python (Basic) Certificate

Raghu S

Sharing Python SDET Jobs | Follow me for updates | 13k+ conn's | Python | PyTest | Full stack SDET | Selenium | API | Cloud | CI/CD | Jenkins | OWASP | API Security | Layer7 | WAF | API | WAAP India

Summary

Proficient IT Professional over 12+ years of experience in software automation testing and automation framework development / enhancements. A highly self motivated and ambitious individual able to give timely and accurate advice, guidance, support and training to team members and individuals. I have worked as an individual contributor and led team in development and automation.

- Currently Working as Staff Engineer at Imperva
- 10+ Years Experience into Test automation
- Experience in Distributed systems and Micro services testing
- Has proficient work experience on Python and related technologies.
 Also worked with PyTest, Robot Framework, API REST, SOAP
 +XML, Selenium WebDriver, Cloud Infra Automation with AWS using
- Terraform etc.

 Proven ability to understand and learn new technologies &
- Good communication & interpersonal skills, self-motivated, quick learner and team player.

Technical Skills

Programming Languages: Python 3.x

applications to solve business problems.

Automation Frameworks: PyTest, Robot Framework

OS: Linux, Windows

Web Technologies: HTML, CSS

Cloud Technologies: AWS, Azure, Terraform

Virtualization Technologies : VMWare VSphere ESXI

Containers : Docker, Kubernetes Web Services: REST, SOAP+XML

Automation : Selenium WebDriver, Requests

Testing Tools: Postman

Collaborating Tools: GitLab, Stash/Bit Bucket, GitHub, JIRA,

Confluence, Zephyr CI / CD Tools : Jenkins

Databases: Postgres, Oracle 19C

IDE: Pycharm

Misc: JSON, SOAP+XML, XML, SQL

Domain Skillsets:

L7, Cyber Security, L3 Network Security, OWASP, Web Application Firewall, API Security

Experience

Imperva

2 years 5 months

Staff Engineer

October 2023 - Present (1 year 4 months)

India

Working on backend automation using Python.

Features:

API Security, WAAP

SOAP+XML, REST API traffic

API Top OWASP Risks testing and automation

Senior QE Engineer

September 2022 - September 2023 (1 year 1 month)

India

Ivanti

Senior Software Development Engineer in Test April 2021 - September 2022 (1 year 6 months)

India

Pulse Secure (acquired by Ivanti)

Network Security Product (VPN) automation tester

Infosys

Test Analyst

February 2018 - April 2021 (3 years 3 months)

Bangalore

Accenture in India
Test Engineering Analyst
March 2016 - January 2018 (1 year 11 months)
Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

Wipro Limited
Test Engineer
February 2013 - March 2016 (3 years 2 months)
Bangalore

Education

Anna University Chennai

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Electrical and Electronics

Engineering · (2008 - April 2012)